## **Muhamad Arif**

Kota Bekasi, Indonesia | mhdarif.dev@gmail.com | +6281314097048 https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhamad-arif-6646a814b/ | https://superb-dodol-3468c6.netlify.app/

|--|

Muhamad Arif, a 23-year-old 5th-semester student at Universitas Gunadarma, is currently pursuing a degree in Computer Science. Over the past year. I have demonstrated a strong blend of hardskills

and softskills through diverse activities, particularly in the field of UI/UX five UI/UX competitions, securing a win in one of them. My expertises my proficiency in tools such as Figma, specifically for web and meeffectively utilize my skills in both academic and practical settings capability in my field.	X design. I have participated in spans various areas, showcasing obile UI design. My ability to
EDUCATION LEVEL	
Undergraduate Informatics, Universitas Gunadarma GPA: 3.55 / 4.00	Sep 2022 - Present
PROJECT EXPERIENCE	
UX Designer UI/UX Competition (Web E-Commerce)   Remote, using Figma	Aug 2023 - Dec 2023
Designing wireframes and interactive prototypes	
☐ Conducting user research	
Link project:	10 1 1 0 70
https://www.figma.com/design/TluiOhqBzqH7zvws7qqZwh/adgency.co.ic 8vd7t-1	1/node-1d=U-1&t=D51
UX Designer UI/UX Competition (Mobile App)  Figma App	Aug 2023 - Dec 2023
Designed high-fidelity prototypes	
Created 10+ high-fidelity screens using Figma, focusing on m contributed to a clear and intuitive user interface.	obile app usability, which
Link project: https://www.figma.com/design/anakAGo7oUuUvX2rsAtYOe/cityWise?nod h-1	e-id=0-1&t=ebBlw4EzJCtW0wl
SKILL & QUALIFICATIONS	
<b>Hard Skill</b> : Mobile App Designer, Web Designer, UX Designer <b>Soft Skill:</b> Analytical thinking, Problem Solving, Leadership, F Management	
ACHIEVEMENTS	

Won 2nd place in the UI/UX competition "Web Xperience Design Challenge" held by Gunadarma University in August 2023 Link Certificate:

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ufcr16KsLntd5L4sDKeM2gtU6YvRIfBB/view?usp=sharing